[
    {"question":"Who was the voice of Scar in 'The Lion King'?", "answer":"Jeremy Irons"},
    {"question":"What does Gru want to steal in 'Despicable Me'?", "answer":"The Moon"},
    {"question":"The Mousekewitzs from 'An American Tail' come from what country?", "answer":"Russia"},
    {"question":"Who did the voice of the vegetarian cat Tiger in 'An American Tail'?", "answer":"Dom DeLuise"},
    {"question":"What is the name of the Corpse Bride in 'Corpse Bride'?", "answer":"Emily"},
    {"question":"What family runs the chicken farm in 'Chicken Run'?", "answer":"The Tweedys"},
    {"question":"What Monty Python member voiced King Harold in 'Shrek 2'?", "answer":"John Cleese"},
    {"question":"Who did the voice of Horton in the movie version of 'Horton Hears a Who'?", "answer":"Jim Carrey"},
    {"question":"John Smith is a character in which animated film?", "answer":"Pocahontas"},
    {"question":"Zazu is a character in which animated film?", "answer":"The Lion King"},
    {"question":"What celebrity does a government ad for the new Grand Canyon in 'The Simpsons Movie'?", "answer":"Tom Hanks"},
    {"question":"Bruce was a character in which animated film?", "answer":"Finding Nemo"}

  ]